Guide to the Bryant Fleming plans, [ca. 1904-1937]
Fleming, Bryant plans
- Series III. Clients R-Y
  - Statler, E. M., Esq. Location: Buffalo, New York
    - Plan of arrangement, 1910 (Folder 15)
      Sheet # 248
    - Planting plan, 1912 (Folder 15)
      Sheet # 249
    - Ground floor plan of residence, by Architects Esenwein & Johnson, Undated (Folder 15)
      Sheet # 250
    - Ground floor plan of residence, by Architects Esenwein & Johnson, Undated (Folder 16)
      Sheet # 251
      Scale: 1/4"=1"
    - Ground floor plan of residence, Undated (Folder 16)
      Sheet # 252
    - Ground floor plan of residence, by Architects Esenwein & Johnson, Undated (Folder 17)
      Sheet # 253
    - Garden side elevation, Undated (Folder 17)
      Sheet # 254
    - Details of cut stone on terrace, by Architects Esenwein & Johnson, Undated (Folder 17)
      Sheet # 255
    - Details of cut stone on terrace, by Architects Esenwein & Johnson, Undated (Folder 17)
      Sheet # 256
    - "A Plan of the grounds" (Probably the plan published in American Country Homes of Today, 1913), Undated (Folder 17)
      Sheet # 257
      Format: Card Stock, likely
    - Plan of arrangement, 1903 (Box 61)
      Sheet # 1800
  - Client: Tarbell, George S. Location: Ithaca, New York
    - Sketch of Fireplace, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 511
    - Plan of arrangement and planting, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 512
    - Written specifications for Chimney construction with sketch, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 513
    - Folder of plans for Boathouse, by architect Clinton L. Vivian, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 514
      Format: Blue Lines
  - Client: Thompson, Mr. & Mrs. A. M. Location: Wildwood, Pennsylvania
    - Perspective sketch of service turn and covered arbor, 1916 (Folder 10)
      Sheet # 106
    - House, Grades, Arrangement, 1916 (Folder 42a)
      Sheet # 1324
      Format: Blueprint 0/6
  - Townsend & Fleming Location: Unspecified
    - Design for Townsend & Fleming seal, Undated (Box 49, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 1534
  - Tovell Location: East Toronto (or unspecified)
    - List of "Rooms Required" in proposed residence, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 1166
      Format: Stationery from the "Regina-Palast Hotel, Munich, Germany
    - Sketch of Fountain, Undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1209
      Format: Crayon on tracing paper
    - Study for Tovell fountain, 1921 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1210
      Format: Ink and pencil on Tracing paper
    - Sketches of Fountain, Undated (Box 42)
      Sheet # 1211
  - University Club of Buffalo Location: Buffalo, New York
    - Plot plan for clubhouse, by Architects Green & Wicks, 1903 (Folder 44a)
      Sheet # 1460
    - Elevation and details, 1904 (Box 48)
      Sheet # 1461
    - Study, 1904 (Folder 44a)
      Sheet # 1462
    - Sketch, likely, Undated (Box 49, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1463
    - Sketch of garden, Undated (Box 49, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1464
    - Plan for estimate, 1905 (Box 48)
      Sheet # 1465
    - Tabulations, 5 pages, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 1466
    - Sketch plan for location of Tennis court, Photocopy, 1904 (Box 48)
      Sheet # 1467
    - Sketch plan for location of Tennis court, 1904 (Box 48)
      Sheet # 1468
    - Description unspecified, Undated (Box 49, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1469
    - Details of the Arbor, 1904 (Box 48)
      Sheet # 1470
    - Sketch, Undated (Box 49, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1471
    - Sketch, Undated (Box 49, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1472
    - Sketch, Undated (Box 49, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1473
    - Sketch of the Arbor, 1905 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1474
    - Elevation details, fence about the arbor, 1904 (Box 48)
      Sheet # 1475
    - Details for the arbor, 1904 (Box 48)
      Sheet # 1476
    - Sketch plan for arrangement, 1904 (Folder 44b)
      Sheet # 1477
      Format: Photocopy
    - Gymnasium building, plans, 1903 (Box 48)
      Sheet # 1478
    - Gymnasium elevations, 1903 (Box 48)
      Sheet # 1479
    - Clubhouse ground floor plan, 1903 (Box 48)
      Sheet # 1480
    - Clubhouse front elevation, 1903 (Box 48)
      Sheet # 1481
    - Clubhouse south elevation, 1903 (Box 48)
      Sheet # 1482
    - Clubhouse rear elevation, 1904 (Box 48)
      Sheet # 1483
    - Clubhouse north elevation, 1904 (Box 48)
      Sheet # 1484
    - Plan for planting, 1904 (Folder 53)
      Sheet # 2002
  - Upson, Mrs. Mary Location: Cleveland, Ohio
    - General working plan of Garden, 1914 (Box 7)
      Sheet # 115
    - Miscellaneous details - Garden, 1914 (Box 61)
      Sheet # 1796
      Format: Blue - Linen
  - Ward, Mrs. L. A. C. Location: Wyoming, New York
    - Topographical survey, 1908 (Folder 11)
      Sheet # 123
  - Warner, Edwin Location: Nashville, Tennessee
    - Survey of property, Undated (Folder 42b)
      Sheet # 1390
    - Topo., Tract survey, Undated (Box 47)
      Sheet # 1391
    - Sketch of property, 1927 (Box 47)
      Sheet # 1392
    - Surveys, 1927 (Box 47)
      Sheet # 1393
    - Survey, 1928 (Folder 42b)
      Sheet # 1394
    - Plan of basement and foundation, 1923 (Folder 50)
      Sheet # 1505
    - Plan of first floor, 1923 (Folder 50)
      Sheet # 1506
    - Plan of second floor, c. 1923 (Folder 50)
      Sheet # 1507
    - Roof plan, 1923 (Folder 50)
      Sheet # 1508
    - Elevation of north side, 1923 (Folder 50)
      Sheet # 1509
    - Elevation of west side, 1923 (Folder 50)
      Sheet # 1510
    - Elevation of south side, 1923 (Folder 50)
      Sheet # 1511
    - Elevation of east side, 1923 (Folder 50)
      Sheet # 1512
    - Suggested development of lots adjacent to Warner, Edwin property, Undated (Folder 53)
      Sheet # 2001
  - Webb, J. W. S. Location: Shaker Heights (Shaker Heights Village), Ohio
    - Front elevation, 1917 (Box 34)
      Sheet # 962
      Note:By architects Steffens & Steffens
    - Right side elevation, 1917 (Box 34)
      Sheet # 963
    - Rear elevation, 1917 (Box 34)
      Sheet # 964
    - Left side elevation, 1917 (Box 34)
      Sheet # 965
    - Basement plan, 1917 (Box 34)
      Sheet # 966
    - First floor plan, 1917 (Box 34)
      Sheet # 967
    - Second floor plan, 1917 (Box 34)
      Sheet # 968
    - Attic plan, 1917 (Box 34)
      Sheet # 969
    - Topographical survey of property, 1917 (Box 35)
      Sheet # 979
    - Detail of walls and steps, 1918 (Folder 35)
      Sheet # 980
    - Full scale detail of Arbor, Undated (Box 35)
      Sheet # 982
    - Study for landscape arrangement, Undated (Box 35)
      Sheet # 983
    - Elevation of Arbor, 1918 (Box 35)
      Sheet # 984
    - Measurements for portion of garden layout, Undated (Box 35)
      Sheet # 985
    - Details of Arbor and Fence, 1918 (Box 35)
      Sheet # 986
    - Detail plan of Arbor, 1918 (Box 35)
      Sheet # 987
    - Detail plan of Arbor, 1918 (Box 35)
      Sheet # 988
    - Sketch plan of arrangement, 1918 (Folder 36)
      Sheet # 989
      Format: Ink, pencil and crayon on Tracing paper
    - Details of shelter and fence, Undated (Box 35)
      Sheet # 990
    - Topographic map, Undated (Folder 36)
      Sheet # 991
    - Topographical survey - partly planted, Undated (Folder 36)
      Sheet # 992
    - Topographic survey, 1917 (Folder 36)
      Sheet # 993
    - First floor plan, Undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 994
    - Details of shelter and fence, Undated (Box 35)
      Sheet # 995
    - General working plan of arrangement, 1918 (Box 35)
      Sheet # 997
    - Preliminary working arrangement for property, Undated (Box 35)
      Sheet # 998
  - Weil, Julius Location: Nashville, Tennessee
    - View towards East lawn from Arrival court terrace, 1929 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 1414
  - Wellsboro Cemetery Location: Wellsboro, Pennsylvania
    - Plan showing plot sub division, 1906 (Folder 53)
      Sheet # 2003
    - General plan, 1905 (Folder 53)
      Sheet # 2004
    - General plan, 1906 (Folder 53)
      Sheet # 2005
    - Topographical map - plan for addition to addition, 1905 (Folder 53)
      Sheet # 2006
    - Change of road between K & G old part, Undated (Box 72)
      Sheet # 2007
    - Part of map of Wellsboro, Undated (Box 72)
      Sheet # 2008
    - Front elevation, Undated (Box 72)
      Sheet # 2009
    - Details for steps, Undated (Box 72)
      Sheet # 2010
    - Rider showing alternative to accompany plan no. 73-5, Undated (Box 72)
      Sheet # 2011
    - Description unspecified, Undated (Box 72)
      Sheet # 2012
    - Small map showing where Riberall Street enters cemetery, Undated (Box 72)
      Sheet # 2013
      Note:Not drawn to scale
    - Study, Undated (Box 72)
      Sheet # 2014
    - Study, Undated (Box 72)
      Sheet # 2015
    - Plan showing lot sub divisions, 1906 (Box 72)
      Sheet # 2016
    - New cemetery, Undated (Box 72)
      Sheet # 2017
    - Rough sketch of plots, Undated (Box 72)
      Sheet # 2018
    - Plan showing lot sub divisions as proposed by Cemetery authorities, 1906 (Box 72)
      Sheet # 2019
    - Plan showing lot sub divisions, 1906 (Box 72)
      Sheet # 2020
    - Topographical map of addition, 1905 (Box 72)
      Sheet # 2021
    - Plan for sub dividing addition, 1905 (Box 72)
      Sheet # 2022
    - Topographical map of addition, 1905 (Box 72)
      Sheet # 2023
    - Plan for addition to cemetery, 1905 (Box 73)
      Sheet # 2024
      Format: Blueprint negative
    - Topographical map of addition, 1905 (Box 73)
      Sheet # 2025
    - Planting plan for addition, 1905 (Box 73)
      Sheet # 2026
    - Planting plan for addition, 1905 (Box 73)
      Sheet # 2035
      Format: Blue (white)
    - Planting plan for addition, 1905 (Box 73)
      Sheet # 2036
    - Preliminary plan for addition, 1905 (Box 73)
      Sheet # 2037
    - Preliminary plan for addition, 1905 (Box 73)
      Sheet # 2038
    - General plan, 1905 (Box 73)
      Sheet # 2039
    - Planting plan for addition, 1905 (Folder 53)
      Sheet # 2040
  - Client: Wilcox, Mrs. Ansley Location: Lake View, New York
    - Sketch of seat in recess of South wall, Undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 1150
  - Williams, Mrs. Halsey Location: Sewickley, Pennsylvania
    - Sections through garden, Undated (Folder 47)
      Sheet # 1430
    - Garden details, Undated (Folder 43b)
      Sheet # 1435
  - Winter, Walter C. Location: Lake Forest, Illinois
    - Sketch and layout of Residence and landscape development, Undated (Folder 43b)
      Sheet # 1419
    - Plan of arrangement, Undated (Folder 43b)
      Sheet # 1420
    - Interior of Drive Passage, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 1423
    - Sketch of service and garage court, 1926 (Box 47)
      Sheet # 1424
    - Perspective of Garage Court, 1926 (Box 47)
      Sheet # 1425
    - Sketch study of arrival court, Undated (Box 47)
      Sheet # 1426
    - Sketch of Loggia- North elevation, 1929 (Box 47)
      Sheet # 1427
    - Sketch study of arrival court, Undated (Box 47)
      Sheet # 1428
    - Details for Son's and Guest's dressing room cases, 1927 (Box 69)
      Sheet # 1974
    - Details of cases in dressing room, 1927 (Folder 52)
      Sheet # 1978
    - Details for Son's and Guest's dressing rooms, 1927 (Folder 52)
      Sheet # 1979
    - Sleeping porch railways, Undated (Folder 53)
      Sheet # 1993
    - Balcony railing, Undated (Folder 53)
      Sheet # 1994
    - Son's and Guest's dressing room cases, 1927 (Folder 53)
      Sheet # 1995
    - Son's and Guest's dressing room cases, 1927 (Folder 53)
      Sheet # 1996
    - Detail of flower room and second floor radiator cover, 1924 (Folder 53)
      Sheet # 1997
    - Details of cases in dressing room, 1927 (Folder 53)
      Sheet # 1998
    - Miscellaneous iron, Undated (Folder 53)
      Sheet # 1999
  - Winter, Mr. & Mrs. Walter C. Location: Lake Forest, Illinois
    - Study for a residence, 1926 (Folder 54)
      Sheet # 1719
  - Woodworth, A. J. Location: Nunda, New York
    - Preliminary study for Property development, 1929 (Folder 12)
      Sheet # 133
  - Wymond, L. H. Location: Glenview, Kentucky
    - Details of Gate posts and Walls at Entrance near Garage, 1914 (Box 6)
      Sheet # 107
      Scale: 1/4"=1'; 1"=1'
    - Topographical plan of property belonging to Wymond, L. H., 1913 (Folder 10)
      Sheet # 108
    - Forecourt and Adjacent features, 1914 (Box 6)
      Sheet # 109
      Scale: 1/8"=1'; 1/2"=1'
    - Details of Tea Garden, 1914 (Box 7)
      Sheet # 110
      Scale: 1/4"=1'; 1"=1', Full scale
  - Location: Jefferson County, Kentucky
    - Tentative plan of entrance drive, 1913 (Box 55)
      Sheet # 1620
    - Topographic map, River road, 1910 (Box 55)
      Sheet # 1621
    - Proposed relocation of River Road, 1913 (Box 55)
      Sheet # 1622
    - Proposed relocation of River Road, 1913 (Box 55)
      Sheet # 1623
    - Proposed relocation of River Road, 1913 (Box 55)
      Sheet # 1624
    - Forecourt and adjacent features, 1914 (Box 55)
      Sheet # 1625
      Format: Blue linen
    - Details of gate posts and of walls at entrance near garage, 1914 (Box 55)
      Sheet # 1626
    - Topographical plan of property, 1913 (Folder 48)
      Sheet # 1629
    - Cross section of proposed relocation of River Road, 1913 (Folder 48)
      Sheet # 1630
  - Yensen, Peter Location: East Cleveland, Ohio
    - Topographical survey, by F. A. Pease engineering company, 1912 (Box 24)
      Sheet # 586
    - Sketch plan for arrangement of property, 1913 (Box 24)
      Sheet # 587
    - Plan for arrangement of property, Undated (Box 24)
      Sheet # 588
    - Planting study for the "Hillside" area, Undated (Box 24)
      Sheet # 589
    - Plan for arrangement of property, Undated (Box 24)
      Sheet # 590
    - Planting list - 4 pages, Undated (Box 24)
      Sheet # 591
    - Sketch plan for arrangement of property, 1913 (Box 24)
      Sheet # 592
    - Planting plan (Incomplete), 1913 (Box 24)
      Sheet # 593
    - General arrangement of "Windermere Hill", Undated (Box 24)
      Sheet # 594
    - Profile of entrance drive, 1913 (Box 24)
      Sheet # 595
    - General arrangement of "Windermere Hill", Undated (Box 24)
      Sheet # 596
    - Details of terrace steps and walls, Undated (Box 25)
      Sheet # 597
    - Alternative sketch for arrangement of terrace to present grade of road, Undated (Box 25)
      Sheet # 598
    - Profiles of roads and walks, Undated (Box 25)
      Sheet # 599
    - Sketch of planting plan for "Hillside" area, Undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 600
    - Planting plan for "Hillside" area, 1913 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 601
    - Rough sketch of steps, Undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 602
    - Details for steps and walls, 1913 (Folder 25)
      Sheet # 603
    - Two schemes for service entry, Undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 604
    - Section through road, Undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 605
    - Perspective sketch of drive, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 606
    - Planting plan for "Hillside" area, 1913 (Box 25)
      Sheet # 607
    - General arrangement of "Windermere Hill", Undated (Box 25)
      Sheet # 608
    - Alternative arrangement of "Windermere Hill", Undated (Box 25)
      Sheet # 609
    - Details for terrace, steps and walls, 1913 (Box 25)
      Sheet # 610
    - Alternative sketch for treatment of wall along drive, Undated (Box 25)
      Sheet # 611
    - Alternative sketch for treatment of wall along drive, Undated (Box 25)
      Sheet # 612
    - Elevation of walls and steps, 1913 (Box 25)
      Sheet # 613
    - Plan of walls as steps, 1913 (Box 25)
      Sheet # 614
    - Details for terrace, steps and walls, 1913 (Box 25)
      Sheet # 615
    - Alternative scheme maintaining the present grade of drive, Undated (Box 25)
      Sheet # 616
    - Alternative scheme maintaining the present grade of drive, 1913 (Box 25)
      Sheet # 617
    - Elevation of walls and steps from the drive, Undated (Box 25)
      Sheet # 618
    - Planting plan, Undated (Box 25)
      Sheet # 619
    - Planting plan, Undated (Box 25)
      Sheet # 620
    - Rough planting scheme, Undated (Box 25)
      Sheet # 621
    - General arrangement of property, 1913 (Box 25)
      Sheet # 622
      Note:
    - Rough sketches for steps, Undated (Box 25)
      Sheet # 623
    - Cross section through porch, Undated (Box 25)
      Sheet # 624
    - General arrangement of "Windermere Hill", Undated (Box 25)
      Sheet # 625
- Unspecified Client - Arranged by Sheet Number
  Notes: Some have likely Clients written in parenthesis. Looking for nearby numbers may give an idea of likely clients but this is not always the case.
  - Unspecified Location: Unspecified
    - Sketch in a Cemetery, Undated (Folder 33)
      Sheet # 838
      Format: Colored chalk on Tracing paper
    - Sketch of entry gates and drive, Undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 839
  - Unspecified Location: Unspecified
    - Perspective sketch of House and Garden, Undated (Folder 33)
      Sheet # 841
  - Unspecified Location: Unspecified
    - Sketch for floral decorative detail, Undated (Box 33)
      Sheet # 847
      Format: Crayon on Tracing paper
  - Unspecified (likely William P. Snyder) Location: Unspecified
    - Perspective sketch in Garden, Undated (Box 33)
      Sheet # 850
    - Perspective in garden, Undated (Box 33)
      Sheet # 852
  - Unspecified(likely Plesset or McKinney) Location: Unspecified
    - Sketch "C" - Four elevations of Garden Structure, Undated (Box 33)
      Sheet # 859
    - Sketch "B" - Four elevations of Garden Structure, Undated (Box 33)
      Sheet # 860
    - South-wets Piers - Garage court, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 861
    - Sketch "A" - Four elevations of garden structure, Undated (Box 33)
      Sheet # 873
    - Construction notes on three attached sheets, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 874
  - Unspecified (likely Plesset or McKinney) Location: Unspecified
    - Plan of addition to residence, likely, Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 877
  - Unspecified (likely Plesset or McKinney) Location: Unspecified
    - Second floor plan, Undated (Box 34)
      Sheet # 894
  - Unspecified (Likely Webb or Hoffman) Location: Unspecified
    - Sewer and lot line, Undated (Folder 35)
      Sheet # 961
  - Unspecified Location: Unspecified
    - Details of overlook, 1921 (Folder 36)
      Sheet # 996
  - Unspecified Location: Unspecified
    - Study of Stable group, Undated (Box 42)
      Sheet # 1151
    - Study of Stable group, Undated (Box 42)
      Sheet # 1152
    - Study of Stable group, Undated (Box 42)
      Sheet # 1153
    - Study of Stable group, Undated (Box 42)
      Sheet # 1154
    - Study of Stable group, Undated (Box 42)
      Sheet # 1155
    - Perspective sketch of Living room, Undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 1156
    - Perspective sketch of Library, Undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 1157
    - South elevation of Library, Undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 1158
    - Sketch of Fireplace in Library, Undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 1159
    - Sketch of Fireplace in Library, Undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 1160
    - Perspective sketch in Library, Undated (Box 42)
      Sheet # 1161
  - Unspecified Location: Unspecified
    - Perspective sketch in stair hall, Undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 1163
    - Perspective sketches in stair hall, Undated (Box 42)
      Sheet # 1164
    - Elevation of main stair hall, Undated (Box 42)
      Sheet # 1165
  - Unspecified Location: Gloversville, NY
    - Herman Myers memorial park, Undated (Folder 42a)
      Sheet # 1323
  - Likely Shepherd or Mengel Location: Unspecified
    - Details of windows, likely, Undated (Box 47)
      Sheet # 1369
    - Details of woodwork, Undated (Box 47)
      Sheet # 1370
    - Details of woodwork, Undated (Folder 42a)
      Sheet # 1371
    - Details of Brick and mortar work, Undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 1372
  - Unspecified Location: Grosse Pointe
    - Topo, 1936 (Box 47)
      Sheet # 1388
  - Likely Schwab, Clements, Cheek, or Warner Location: Unspecified
    - Study, Residence and Grounds, Undated (Folder 42b)
      Sheet # 1396
  - Unspecified Location: Unspecified
    - The Cortile, Sketch, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 1406
    - Terrace Terminal, Sketch, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 1407
    - The Cortile, Sketch, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 1408
    - View of Gardens, Sketch, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 1409
    - View from Lawn towards main Terrace sketch, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 1410
    - View looking down Long Terrace, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 1411
    - View from Pool garden, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 1412
    - Garage court, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 1413
  - Unspecified Location: Unspecified
    - Chandelier, Undated (Folder 51)
      Sheet # 1513
    - Entryway details, likely, Undated (Folder 51)
      Sheet # 1514
  - Unspecified Location: Wisconsin
    - Map of Sylvania Club property - reverse is sketch with measurements for residence, 1916 (Box 49, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 1535
  - Unspecified Location: Unspecified
    - First floor plan, Undated (Box 49, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 1536
    - Piazza details, likely, Undated (Box 49, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 1537
  - Unspecified Location: Unspecified
    - Floor plan, Undated (Box 49, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 1539
    - Exterior of building, Undated (Box 49, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 1540
    - Exterior of building, Undated (Box 49, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 1541
    - Exterior of building, Undated (Box 49, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 1542
    - Exterior of building, Undated (Box 49, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 1543
    - Landscape design, Undated (Box 49, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 1544
    - Landscape design, Undated (Box 49, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 1545
    - Colonial garden check and settee in chestnut, 1912 (Box 49, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 1546
    - Detail - Balustrade, likely, Undated (Box 49, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 1547
    - Exterior details, Undated (Box 49, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 1548
    - Detail of Balustrade, Undated (Box 49, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 1549
    - Front elevation, Undated (Box 49, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 1550
    - Balustrade, Undated (Box 49, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 1551
    - Piazza, Undated (Box 49, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 1552
  - Unspecified Location: Unspecified
    - Triangle at Erie, Swan and Pearls streets, Undated (Box 49, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 1554
    - Plan No. 41.4 - Sketch for stone coping, Undated (Box 49, Folder 6)
      Sheet # 1555
  - Unspecified Location: Unspecified
    - Unidentified drawing with elevations, Undated (Box 52)
      Sheet # 1564
  - Unspecified Location: Unspecified
    - Sketch of pool, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1617
    - Dimensions, Undated (Box 49, Folder 6)
      Sheet # 1618
    - Perspective of first scheme, now changed, Undated (Box 49, Folder 6)
      Sheet # 1619
  - Townsend & Fleming Location: Hudson, NY
    - Sketch of Playhouse, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1650
      Note:By J. S. Comstock
    - Sketch of Playhouse, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1651
    - Sketch of Playhouse, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1652
  - Unspecified Location: Unspecified
    - Rough pencil sketches and figures, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1653
      Format: 3 pages Legal Papers, Small Tracing
    - Sketched details - veranda, Undated (Box 49, Folder 6)
      Sheet # 1654
  - Unspecified Location: Unspecified
    - Road/Drive profiles, Undated (Box 58)
      Sheet # 1661
  - Unspecified Location: Unspecified
    - Elevation, Undated (Box 60)
      Sheet # 1702
  - Unspecified Location: Unspecified
    - Landscape details, Undated (Box 61)
      Sheet # 1797
  - Unspecified Location: Unspecified
    - Advertising sketch leaf - Joseph P. McHugh & Sons, McHugh willow furniture, 1909 (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1855
    - Section though typical vitrified pipe catch basin, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1856
    - Grading, Undated (Box 10)